3, 2, 1, let's go!
Three, two, one, let's go!
Three, two, one!
Let's go in three, two, one!
We've started practicing the extras!
Let's go 3, 2, 1!
Good morning
Good morning.
Today is already December, so I want to feel Christmas
I've put on my Christmas knitwear.
I'm going to get excited with this
I'll try my best on this last day.
I've been getting a lot of requests to make it an "aha up" look.
So I made it an "aha" up!
Please pay attention, everyone!
I did a twist today.
I did it with my cousin.
It's a little different.
Hey, Cousin.
So cute!
Cute.
You don't think.
I have to go find someone.
Who brought it?
Did I bring it?
The turtle outside?
Tanitani.
That's the first time anyone's said that to me.
Pokemon Ramen.
I won a Papimocci just now.
You said something.
Cute doggie.
No, it's not.
I don't know.
Ouch!
Wait, Ali should've made that face.
Not even close.
Not at all.
You look like you're having a good time.
From now on, let's see...
We have rehearsal.
It's pretty short time, isn't it?
We don't have a lot of time today, so we're going to discuss it with everyone with an eye on the horizontal rows, so
I'm going to concentrate a little bit and do my best.
Thank you for your performance this morning.
I'll do my best after all this time. My best regards to you.
Best regards.
I'll do my best. Best regards. The show was last week. I'll do my best.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll do my best.
Odagura-chan, if you don't get in front of the audience, you're going to get stuck in here.
Yes, sir.
But it's almost over, so I'd like to do a little more.
In the first performance, the choreography was very tight.
The choreography was so tight.
Everyone was checking each other's moves until the very last minute.
But now that we have Anila, I've seen the performance of our seniors and I think it's great.
I think we were able to learn a lot from them.
I think we can take advantage of this opportunity while absorbing that as well.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm grateful for the opportunity and will do my best.
You're here, aren't you?
You're still here.
How was it?
I don't like it.
I want you to take a side shot.
I want to show you the backside.
Come on, Airi, watch this side.
It's okay.
That's good.
Look this way.
Look here.
Like this.
Mental.
Now I'm backstage.
I'm always surrounded by these mirrors.
I think we're going to have a rehearsal for the shadows, so let's take a peek.
Thank you very much for watching.
These pens were given to us by our seniors.
We all have the same pens in our third term.
I got an avocado pen.
They're playing a cute game of rock-paper-scissors.
It's hard to get started, isn't it?
Good morning.
Third graders' school holiday dream.
Long sleeves, okay?
Good luck with that. It's very important.
Now, I'm going to eat ramen noodles for the noon show, because it's almost noon.
Bye bye.
I hope you all eat ramen too.
What are you having, Nio-chan?
I'm going to eat this.
Strawberries are growing.
It's cool.
What'll you have for your pig's lunch?
Oranges, bi-nuts, and strawberries.
I'm with you.
Fynapple.
Delicious.
I'm off.
Muscat.
Oh, yeah. I've decided on a bang.
Bang at the top.
Let's focus, seriously.
I hope they think it's great after all.
It's a daytime show. What do you think?
What do you think? Two more shows.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Wow.
But I'm really sad to think that the show will be over after two performances,
So I really don't want to regret it,
I want to give it my all.
I might want to see it.
Power.
Three, two, one, let's go!
Always be gorgeous and strong, blooming like cherry blossoms!
The line "just dazzling".
Bloom, Sakurazaka 46
Bloom in full bloom!
Thank you very much for coming to Theater Minanoza's opening series, Niiza Mono Live at Theater Minanoza today!
I'm Reina Odakura from Sakurazaka 46.
I'm Yu Mura.
The show will begin shortly.
Sakura-ka 463rd term newcomers, the 9th show.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching
I've put it all out there for now without thinking about this 10th one.
I have the next Kagenare!
It's the 10th one, so I'm going to give it a shot.
I'll do my best for the 10th one.
Why are you using it while eating lunch?
I don't have much time. I need to cool my feet.
We're in the Warriors' time.
We can even eat our lunches.
It's delicious.
I'm used to it. At first I could only do it for 3 seconds.
You've really grown up, haven't you?
These new balls.
When it reaches Itoh's level, it runs out.
Here, Airi, put it on for me.
No, I can do it.
I can do it.
But Ito, have her put it on.
Ito, I disagree.
Thank you... you're doing a perfect job.
Thank you.
Cut.
I'm thinking of doing a double encore for the final night performance.
And we're going to perform "The Future If You Talk" by Keyakizaka46 with the 3rd term students.
Okay! Last, last, last!
I'm sure you'll be able to see that many of the hiragana will be like this, so please keep them facing forward,
This time, I'm going to do Dun mouth with excellence.
I'll be praying for you.
How's it going? After the rehearsal.
We only had two performances on stage, so I think everyone has their own concerns,
But I think it means that they wanted to entrust the music of Keyakizaka 46 to the 3rd term students,
And since this is the last time for the newcomers, I hope we can give our all without any regrets.
Tour, anila, newcomers, two performances a day.
And new songs for everyone. You faced an incredibly hard schedule. So thank you so much.
I'm very happy about that and I'm enjoying making things together with the third term students.
I am looking forward to being in the audience today.
Have a good day.
Please go.
Even if you cry, it is the last time, so let's really get into it and do our best.
Let's help each other if we have any problems, and let's all look at each other and enjoy the last performance.
3, 2, 1, here we go!
Be strong and gorgeous, bloom like cherry blossoms!
Jansplus no yanself
sake sakurazaka46
In full bloom!
Thank you very much for coming to today's opening series of Theater Mira-no-za, Live Art Theater Mira-no-za at the Niiza Gate.
The show will begin shortly.
Are you ready to get excited?
Can you all shout out "3rd term students"?
Are you ready to shout with the 3rd term students?
Will you make memories with the 3rd term students?
Do you love them?
Let's make a great show together tonight!
Yes!
Thank you for watching!
Sakurazaka, third term students
Sakurazaka, third term
Sakurazaka, 3rd term
Sakurazaka, third term students
We, the third term students
with all our hearts
What our seniors have cherished
that our seniors have cherished.
Please listen to us.
If you want to talk about the future
Thank you for watching
You did a really good job.
It's happening again.
How many times? How many times today?
I'm so glad that you guys feel the same way.
I'm so glad that you all feel the same way.
I think it was a really wonderful concert.
Take a good rest today.
Give yourself a lot of praise.
I'm so proud of you for being so great!
You sang some crazy sweet lyrics.
Thank you so much for your hard work!
thank you so much
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you for your hard work.
I've noticed that the days when I get compliments on my MC
I realized that it was a day when I didn't think about everything.
I started to think that it would be better to speak from my feelings on the spot
I started to think that it would be better to speak from my feelings on the spot.
I think that all the 3rd term students are helping me.
And all of my buddies are helping me too.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
It came naturally.
I think I did it a little bit naturally.
I got it done.
It was a lot of fun.
But I don't want this to be the end.
I don't want this to be the end.
You have to be together in your heart to make it.
And I realized that.
I love you all so much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Welcome back.
Looks delicious!
Thank you so much for your hard work!